question_data = [
         {
             "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
             "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
             "question": "There are 6 legendary cards in Clash Royale.",
             "correct_answer": "False",
             "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
         },
         {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "Pac-Man was invented by the designer Toru Iwatani while he was eating pizza.",
          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
         {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "Tetris is the #1 best-selling video game of all-time.", "correct_answer": "False",
          "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
         {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "Gordon Freeman, the protagonist of Half-Life is said to have once had a ponytail.",
          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
         {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon Sun and Moon, a male Salandit can evolve to a Salazzle.",
          "correct_answer": "False",
          "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
         {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Arbok evolves into Seviper.",
          "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
         {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "The ghosts in Pac-Man&quot and Ms. Pac-Man have completely different behavior.",
          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
         {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "Activision created Battlefield 1.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
         {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "Doki Doki Literature Club was developed in Japan.", "correct_answer": "False",
          "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
         {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
          "question": "In the video game Splatoon;, the playable characters were originally going to be rabbits instead of squids.",
          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}


]
